A Guide to the Papers of Edgar Finley Shannon 1837-1996
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Scrapbooks, Photograph Albums, Other Bound Volumes, and Memorabilia (Box 14-18)
  - Scrapbook - Shannon's Retirement 1973 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Scrapbook - Shannon's Retirement 1973 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Scrapbook - Commission on CIA Activities within the United States (Rockefeller Commission) 1975 (Box-folder 18:6)
- Series V: Restricted Papers
  19
  - Grade Books 1951-1988 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Washington and Lee University applications 1984 (Box-folder 19:2)